{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Matthew_Sciabarra",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Chris Matthew Sciabarra",
    "human_readable": "Chris Matthew Sciabarra is labeled as 'Chris Matthew Sciabarra'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.951601505279541,
            "question": "Who is Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.915985107421875,
            "question": "What is known about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8818243145942688,
            "question": "Are there any publications or works associated with Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8645117878913879,
            "question": "Where might I find more information about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8541683554649353,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Chris Matthew Sciabarra's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101320862770081,
            "question": "What are some key facts about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7857416868209839,
            "question": "Can you summarize what you know about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820749878883362,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7577188014984131,
            "question": "Is Chris Matthew Sciabarra connected to any organizations or institutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6730650067329407,
            "question": "What field might Chris Matthew Sciabarra specialize in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Matthew Sciabarra is labeled as 'Chris Matthew Sciabarra'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3766_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Chris Matthew Sciabarra connected to any organizations or institutions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3766_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3766_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you summarize what you know about Chris Matthew Sciabarra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3766_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3766_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3766/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt) contains the line \"Chris Matthew Sciabarra has been a Visiting Scholar in the Department of Politics at New York University since 1989.\" and another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3766/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt) contains the line \"Chris Matthew Sciabarra is Visiting Scholar in the Department of Politics at New York University.\", which together provide enough information to label Chris Matthew Sciabarra as 'Chris Matthew Sciabarra'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information supports the statement \"Chris Matthew Sciabarra is labeled as 'Chris Matthew Sciabarra'\". All provided documents consistently refer to the individual in question by his full name, Chris Matthew Sciabarra."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}